## STEPHANIE HOTCHKISS

905-510-7050

stephbarone@gmail.com

Stephanie is outgoing, determined and hard working. Her various life experiences allow her to be a well rounded person and employee. She is punctual, respectful and enjoys working with others and meeting new people. Her joy and passion for life and adventure follow her into every workplace, which inspires herself and others to do their best.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**RESIDENT MUSICIAN, FIRST UNITARIAN CONGREGATION OF TORONTO - SEPT 2012 - PRESENT** Soprano Section Lead and Soloist for the choir and congregation.

#### SOPRANO SOLOIST, NATHANIEL DETT CHORALE — OCT 2010 - PRESENT

I sing in the soprano section and am a soloist at times.

#### SUPERVISOR/AMBASSADOR, PROMOSTAFF, TORONTO - SEPT 2013 - PRESENT

I have worked as an event supervisor, ensuring our team is doing their jobs to the best of their ability. I work with the event co-ordinator and make sure the events run smoothly. I also delegate tasks, breaks and make sure my team is working well together. I have been chosen to be on the roster for PromoStaff because of my personal skills, acting skills and customer service expertise. I have worked on many projects where I commanded large groups made up of the general public and I was able to convey clearly the promotion I was offering. I have been given very positive feedback from my colleagues as well as my clients.

#### **AMBASSADOR. TORONTO BLUE JAYS - MARCH 2012 - PRESENT**

This is my third season with the Toronto Blue Jays. I work in a group of 30 people as customer service specialists called the Ambassadors. We are trained in all aspects of the ball park and our main objective is to help in any situation that may arise with our guests. We are there to make sure our guests safely enjoy the game while having their needs met. To be successful in this position, you must be very personable, work well in a team atmosphere and demonstrate leadership skills.

#### AIR CANADA ROUGE, FLIGHT ATTENDENT, YYZ - APRIL 2014 - JUNE 2014

I have gone through extensive safety training in Toronto and customer service training at Disney World in Orlando Florida. I am the face of Air Canada Rouge on board and serve the passengers while they are on route to their destinations. I am successful at this position because of my love for customer service, working in team atmospheres and traveling. It is a demanding job mentally and physically and demands every employee to be natural leaders.

## MUSIC DIRECTOR, ROLE CALL THEATRE, TORONTO - SEPT 2013 - SEPT 2014

I worked alongside the Director and Choreographer to create a fun and exciting semester of Musical Theatre in an after school program. I am the Musical Director for many different productions.

## FITNESS CONSULTANT/TEACHER CURVES QUEENS PARK, TORONTO - JANUARY 2013 - SEPT 2013

Working in a team with two others, running the women's only gym and making sure our clients are pleased with our club and their workout goals. I work in sales as well as customer service. I also teach many classes. I have made my own class called "ab buster" and "booty shake". These classes are high impact, boot camp classes for our clients.

## MAKING PAWPRINTS INC. — SEPTEMBER 2010 - NOVEMBER 2012

I worked as an independent contractor in Oakville/Mississauga as a dog walker and boarder. I also trained others in this position.

### TEACHER'S ASSISTANT, IRONBARK CAMPUS, QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA — JAN 2009 - AUG 2009

Was chosen to become a teacher's assistant because of my previous leadership skills and courses in high school. I lived as a Don to 40 grade 9 students, ages 14 on an organic working farm in Crow's Nest, Queensland, Australia. I learned how to farm live stock as well as fruits and vegetables. The kids would come for five weeks at a time and I was responsible for leading them on camping trips, farm chores, hiking etc.

# STEPHANIE HOTCHKISS

#### **EDUCATION**

Disney University - Air Canada Rouge Class 2.5. May 2014. Orlando, Florida, USA.

In affiliation with Air Canada Rouge, I graduated from Disney's University geared towards In-Flight Services and over-all Customer Service.

**Dalhousie University** - Class of 2010. Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada.

Bachelor of Arts with distinction combined honours in Music and Theatre

Appleby College - 2005. Oakville, Ontario, Canada.

Graduated with Honours

#### SKILLS

Piano. Voice (Country, Musical Theatre, Classical, Opera, Pop, Jazz). Teaching. Strong communication skills. Strong organizational skills. Team player. Welcoming. Strong computer skills (microsoft office, word, excel, outlook, powerpoint, Mac programs). Time manages very well, First Aid.